

PERSONAL INFORMATION



Erbil, Iraq



+964 751 715 3977



fadi.abd.almassih@gmail.com



01/01/1998

LANGUAGES

Arabic ★★★★★ English ★★★

FADI ABD ALMASSIH

ECONOMIST

ABOUT

I am a confident, competent and self-motivated Economics graduate with over 4 years working experience undertaking marketing and accounting work, whilst working in team environment with tight deadlines, full of passion for learning and developing new skills.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sales Representative

Ibn-Alhaytham Co. | Feb 2020 - Dec 2021

(Homs, Syria)

- Selling medical products to pharmacies throughout the sales territory.
- Coordinate with all sales parties in the company to complete the sales process
- Advising clients on the products, providing technical knowledge.
- Building long term relationships with clients and offering flexible solutions.
- Target always achieved.

Head Cashier

Al-Mahatta Cooperative | Aug 2017 - Jun 2019

(Homs, Syria)

- Trusted to open and close the store, including balancing the cash drawer.
- Update knowledge of new store merchandise weekly.
- Successfully handled customer complaints by resolving issues.
- Trained new employees in cashiering procedures.

Art Director

Cultural Theater | Jan 2019 - Nov 2019

(Homs, Syria)

- Directed 2 plays for amateurs that was played at the Cultural Theater.
- Organized and managed actors and technicians.
- Bridged communication between production staff, actors, and technicians.

Supervisor

Orthodox Association for Helping the Poor | Jan 2015 - Nov 2019 (Homs, Syria)

- Doing administration about the people who need help.
- Giving Humanitarian aid to people in need in and after war.
- Keep in touch with the people in need.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- Excellent ability working with Microsoft Office set (Word, Excel,...)
- Fast Learner
- Leadership experience
- Excellent communication and persuasion skills
- Team player
- Collaboration skills
- Problem-solving abilities
- Decisions making
- Open to new ideas

INTERESTS

- Traveling
- Sports
- Camping
- Donating blood
- Riding bicycle
- Acting

REFERENCES

Upon request

EDUCATION

Economics

Al-Baath University | 2015 - 2021 Bachelor's degree in Economics, Business Administration. (Homs, Syria)

Acting

Cultural Theater | May 2016 - Oct 2019 (Homs, Syria)

Scientific Baccalaureate

Al Ghassania Private School | 2015 (Homs, Syria)

COURSES & CERTIFICATES

Project Management: The Basics for Success

Coursera | 2019

Successful Negotiation: Essential Strategies and Skills

Coursera | 2019

Preparing to Manage Human Resources

Coursera | 2019

Fundamentals of Project Planning and Managament

Coursera | 2019

The Concepts of Sales & Marketing

Business Solutions Center | Certificate No. SYR190832173 | 2019

Business Management Basics

Business Solutions Center | Certificate No. SYR190887120 | 2019

Human Resources Management L1 & L2

Business Solutions Center | Certificate No. SYR190925215 | 2019

Volunteering for helping refugees

Orthodox Social Development Center | 2021

Theater Training

Earned a scholarship with Tawk Community for 2 weeks training in Lebanon | 2018

Actor Prepare

Ministry of Culture in Syria | 2017